<overviews>
    <packages>
        <package name="com.rosettastone.library.taskmanager">
            <shortDescription>
                <![CDATA[
                    The &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt; framework provides an easy mechanism for constructing and executing complex sequences of operations. 
                ]]>
            </shortDescription>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
	                &lt;p&gt;
	                    The &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt; framework provides an easy mechanism for constructing and executing complex sequences of operations.
	                    Each operation is encapsulated in a &lt;code&gt;Task&lt;/code&gt; and can be associated with other operations in a variety of ways.
	                    This framework also provides a number of useful, reusable tasks for performing common operations.
	                    For example, here is how you could use the provided &lt;code&gt;PlaySoundTask&lt;/code&gt; to play a sound:
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;div class="listing"&gt;
                    &lt;pre&gt;
var playSoundTask:PlaySoundTask =
	new PlaySoundTask( aLoadedSoundObject )
		.withCompleteHandler( completeHandler )
		.withErrorHandler( errorHandler )
		.run();
                    &lt;/pre&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;
                    	In the above example, the &lt;code&gt;completeHandler&lt;/code&gt; would be executed when the &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt; completed playing successfully.
                    	If something went wrong during playback the &lt;code&gt;errorHandler&lt;/code&gt; would be called.
                    	This is not very useful in and of itself however as the &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt; class already provides a pretty easy interface for playing audio.
                    	But what if we wanted to create a chain of tasks that played a &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt; once a piece of UI was initialized?
                    	This is also a bit of an arbitrary example but let's take a look at the syntax:
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;div class="listing"&gt;
                    &lt;pre&gt;
var waitForUIInitialization:WaitForUIInitialization = new WaitForUIInitialization( uiComponent );
var playSound:PlaySoundTask = new PlaySoundTask( loadedSound );

var waitForInitializationAndPlaySoundTask:CompositeTask =
	new CompositeTask(
		[ waitForUIInitialization, playSound ], false )
	.withCompleteHandler( completeHandler )
	.withErrorHandler( errorHandler )
	.run() as CompositeTask;
                    &lt;/pre&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;
                    	In the above example, our sound is not played until the previous task has completed.
                    	If something goes wrong with the first task our &lt;code&gt;errorHandler&lt;/code&gt; will be called and our &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt; will not be played.
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;
                    	Using the &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt; (or helper its tasks) it is easy to assemble a large sequence of operations that have dependencies on each other.
                    	One more example (although still a bit arbitrary) would be if we wanted to load an external file, wait for a &lt;code&gt;UIComponent&lt;/code&gt; to initialize, and then play a sound once both of those operations had completed.
                    	Here's how we could set that up with &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt;:
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;div class="listing"&gt;
                    &lt;pre&gt;
var loadFileTask:URLRequestTask = new URLRequestTask( urlRequest );
var waitForUIInitialization:WaitForUIInitialization = new WaitForUIInitialization( uiComponent );
var playSound:PlaySoundTask = new PlaySoundTask( loadedSound );

var taskManager:TaskManager = new TaskManager();
taskManager.addTask( loadFileTask );
taskManager.addTask( waitForUIInitialization );
taskManager.addTask( playSound, [ loadFileTask, waitForUIInitialization ] );
taskManager.run();
                    &lt;/pre&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;
                    	In the above example, the &lt;code&gt;TaskManager&lt;/code&gt; is configured to execute the URL loading task and the &lt;code&gt;UIComponent&lt;/code&gt;-related task immediately.
                    	The task that plays our &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt; however is marked as dependent upon the other 2 tasks and so the &lt;code&gt;TaskManager&lt;/code&gt; will not execute it until they have both successfully completed.
                    	If either one fails then the &lt;code&gt;TaskManager&lt;/code&gt; will dispatch an error event and our &lt;code&gt;Sound&lt;/code&gt;-playing task will not be executed.
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;
                    	Although the convenience tasks provided with the &lt;code&gt;TaskManager&lt;/code&gt; are useful, the real power of this framework can be seen when you create your own operations.
                    	This is typically done by extending &lt;code&gt;Task&lt;/code&gt; or using a generic helper task like &lt;code&gt;TaskWithClosure&lt;/code&gt;.  
                    	Check out each of the classes below to see what kind of objects you have to build upon.
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                ]]>
            </description>
        </package>
        <package name="com.rosettastone.library.taskmanager.events">
            <shortDescription>
                <![CDATA[
                    This package contains classes that define events used by the &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt; framework.
                ]]>
            </shortDescription>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    This package contains classes that define events used by the &lt;code&gt;Task Manager&lt;/code&gt; framework.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </package>
    </packages>
</overviews>